And then all types of violence really increase.
What one thinks first is physical violence, but it may also
be mental violence so that one calls someone for
horrible things and trying to break down self -esteem,
It can be sexual violence
And it can be neglect both by children but perhaps also for the elderly who depend on help
from his family.
What can you do if you see that someone is exposed?
You mean if, for example, you are a relative?
Yes, or if you see in your job that someone seems to be affected?
But I think that risk may be taken
If one compares to that
Children get exposed for a long time
And no one has sounded alarm.
Can you see that more notifications are made in coronatids?
I do not know if they do not know, but I know that there are more calls for example to
women's shelters or to
Children calling to BRIS or Save the Children
And have questions about home violence where they live.